= www.kisskh.asia =
SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
- Morning.
- Morning, Mr. Luan.
Can I clean your office now?
Yes.
Shang Zhitao.
Why didn't you send me
the meeting minutes of the business trip?
If you have forgotten about it,
then you can consider resigning today.
I did send it to you.
I finished everything that night,
and I sent it to you and Lumi.
Where did you send it?
I didn't receive anything.
Your e-mail.
I did send it.
There's another Luke in the company.
Are you aware of that?
Luke Liu.
Check your mailbox.
If you sent it to the wrong recipient,
that would be a breach of confidentiality.
That's worse than forgetting to send it.
Now, make sure
to send your resignation letter
to the right address.
Luke Liu?
REPAYING FAVOR WITH YOUR LIFE
- Flora.
- Lumi.
The filming proposal has been approved.
We'll head to the location tomorrow.
But I checked the weather forecast,
and it says there will be
a heavy rainstorm tomorrow.
You know what? In a while,
we'll discuss the filming
contingency plan with Luke.
I…
Can I still join?
Of course.
I've talked to Luke.
You'll come with me.
But I sent the e-mail to the wrong person.
God knows if I can stay here or not.
Listen.
Just do two things well.
Firstly, do what you need to do.
Ace the filming of this commercial.
Secondly,
forget what Luke said.
So I won't be fired?
You won't.
If they fire you,
who is going to work for me?
Besides, we're having
the filming tomorrow.
It's too late to onboard a new person.
Don't worry.
I'll help you stay.
- Thank you, Lumi.
- Sure.
You work at Lime now?
But
I don't know if I'll pass the probation.
Thank you.
Getting into Lime
already gives you bragging rights
at your alma mater.
To survive in Beijing,
you have to go through trial and error.
If you fail, you pay for the lesson.
If you succeed, celebrate it. Drink it.
Oh. How's your boyfriend, Xin Zhaozhou?
Where is he working?
We broke up before graduation.
His mom wanted him
to apply to be a civil servant.
He asked me to move with him,
but I said no.
He could travel.
Why couldn't he move to Beijing?
That's just life, I guess.
He wants to stay in the south.
I want to stay in the north.
We don't have a choice.
It's okay.
Lime has the classiest men
in all of Beijing.
Have a few relationships.
Experience them while you're young.
It's my boss.
I have to take this.
Hi. This is the dessert to go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I knew it. My client suddenly arrived.
I need to head back now.
I packed two portions. Take them with you.
You barely ate.
Keep one for yourself.
I only found out
that you had already footed the bill
when I asked them to pack the food.
But I told you it would be my treat.
Buying me a meal
when you just found a job?
Come on.
Thanks.
You have already outperformed
95% of fresh graduates
by coming to Beijing alone.
Tao, you can do this. Make sure you stay.
When you're inside,
you always stand a chance.
Don't worry.
I will see it through.
Lumi.
Are you okay? Are you unwell?
They can't confirm
the filming site with me.
It's annoying.
Plus, I'm on my period. My tummy hurts.
Come.
Drink this. I brought goji berry brew.
Have some. While it's hot.
When push comes to shove,
we'll stop somewhere.
Take a break. Don't act tough.
It's fine. I can endure this.
We need to set everything up early.
Luke might drop by at night.
He…
He's coming?
Don't be so anxious.
He just has high standards.
He sounds mean, but he isn't.
You'll see why working with him
is a good thing as time goes by.
Luke is not the hypocritical sort.
Thank you.
TAOBAO
Look.
Don't tell me
- you brought your own bedding.
- I did.
I expected a basic living condition,
given that it's a village,
but I didn't expect it to be this bad.
You're provident.
I'm impressed.
You have a bright future ahead of you.
- Can I have this?
- Take it.
Lumi,
I'll check the next village
to see if they have hot water.
I'll bring some to you.
Don't make your bed. Just lie down.
I'll help you later.
Mr. Liu.
Cancel today's itinerary. Just go back.
Lumi.
I got you two bottles of hot water.
I was thinking
I'll prepare cup noodles for you.
Okay? You can eat something.
Are you serious?
I think you just saved my life.
The bag!
Mister. Quick.
To the filming site. Now.
‪-Coming through.
‪-Over here.
We need to confirm the time with him.
It's mainly because of the weather.
I checked the weather forecast.
It says it won't rain,
but it's cloudy now.
We'll start shooting
when the actors are here.
- Okay.
- Lumi.
Tracy sent me over to help out.
I'm Kitty, from Division Three.
Kitty, is it?
The Excel sheet
is in the shared OA system.
- Okay.
- Take a look.
We'll have a meeting
with the director later
- to confirm the plan before we shoot.
- Okay.
This is Shang Zhitao from my division.
Hello.
Still unwell?
Let's go to the hospital.
It's fine. I just need to sit for a while.
Show this to her. Bring her up to date.
Kitty., hold the fort here.
I'll take Lumi back first.
And take a look at this.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Come. I'm done.
Let's go to the hospital.
Stop acting tough.
- I'm fine.
- Come.
I…
Call me if anything comes up.
Okay.
Did someone corner you at home again?
It must be Zhang Xin.
She came to my shop once.
I said you and I were no longer friends
and asked her to leave.
How does she know where I live?
I'm not surprised.
Women become Sherlock Holmes
when they are obsessed with you.
It's easy to find where you live.
You should head to your parents' mansion
in the suburb and hide there.
We'll see.
I have to head to the filming site
and take a walk there.
- I'll take your car.
- Go ahead. Drive safe.
No wonder you're rich.
You can earn money
while running away from a girl.
Drive safe.
Guys, we have to make it quick today.
Finish it while the sun is up.
It'll rain soon.
Yes, Mr. Director.
Attention!
Wrap it up while the sun is up!
Kitty.
I thought we were supposed
to have the meeting when I came back.
Time is running out.
The director said
it'd rain in the afternoon,
so I had them start earlier.
You must be new.
First time leading a project?
- Yes.
- Oh.
The director said
there are some backup props
we haven't bought.
The driver told me
you had been here before.
I need to make some important calls.
Can I bother you to buy those props?
Sure.
Hold the fort then.
- Keep me updated in the group chat.
- I don't need you to tell me that.
COSTUME DEPARTMENT
Strong precipitation is expected
in the next few hours.
Please take the necessary precautions.
Kitty.
- I bought the props.
- Good.
The actor for the evening scene
complained that our accommodation
was too bad. They refused to come here.
Can you check if there are
better accommodations nearby?
The accommodation is very bad.
I understand why they complain.
Sure.
Mister, how long till we get there?
That village is quite remote.
But worry not,
it's exactly what you're looking for.
If the room is decent,
ask more villagers to spare us some rooms.
With a beautiful lady
like you staying over,
everyone will prepare their beds nicely
and warm them up for you.
‪Hello, Mr. Luan.
Hello, Mr. Luan.
- Hello, Mr. Luan.
Mr. Luan, what brought you here?
Where are Lumi and Shang Zhitao?
Lumi is sick.
Flora went to find new accommodation.
She hasn't returned yet.
The accommodation we found was quite bad.
The actors don't want to stay there,
and their car has broken down.
The other cars
are at the foot of the mountain,
so I asked a villager
to find new accommodation with Flora.
Why didn't you go?
We agreed on the work delegation.
What makes you think
you can delegate work?
Sorry. The user you called
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Stop the shoot. Be on standby.
- Call the police. Find her.
- Shang Zhitao!
Shang Zhitao!
The girl looking for rooms
went to the mountain.
The back mountain is full of steep slopes.
It might collapse anytime.
There could also be rockfalls.
You'll die if you go in.
It's just right in front.
Once we're in the village,
we'll find a shelter first.
Once the rain stops,
I'll ride back with you.
Mister. The rain is too heavy.
Let's turn back. Just forget it.
I have not seen this road before.
This isn't how we came here.
It's raining. This is a shortcut.
The road condition is awful.
Just cling to me.
- Come. Come.
- Hey, you…
Come.
LANDSLIDE WARNING, NO ENTRY
Luan Nian!
Luan Nian! Luan Nian!
It's dangerous here.
Find a safe place first.
Forget about me. Go now.
Go now!
Shang Zhitao.
Are you okay?
I just sprained my ankle.
It hurts when I move.
Your hand is bleeding.
Hang in there.
We should get out as soon as possible.
There might be landslides.
Put these on.
Did I do it right?
There are falling rocks.
We have to take another route.
Listen to my command later.
Do not thrash around.
No matter what happens, do not let go.
Hug me tightly.
Slowly.
Let's rest here.
Are we safe now?
For now, yes.
There should be a village right in front.
Sit down.
How come you came?
Venturing alone in this remote place?
Must a rookie like you work
this hard even in this dire situation?
No one could reach you,
so everyone came to find you.
Fortunately, you are fine.
Put this on.
Sorry. I've troubled
the company once again.
It might hurt a little. Bear with me.
Thank you.
Don't move. I'm more cautious
than you are.
If you become a cripple,
you can always come to work
in your wheelchair.
You're injured.
It's quite serious.
I'm fine.
We're in the same boat.
Let me dress the wound for you.
Sorry.
I'm fine.
Does it hurt?
Get up.
Take this.
Come.
When I was stuck inside,
I felt hopeless.
I thought
that for my first project in Lime,
I would be on the social news.
In my projects,
only my client's ads
get to be on the news.
Not my subordinates.
I was also thinking
that I would die, but I hadn't left
any last words for my parents.
What would you have said?
I…
I would never have the chance
to repay their kindness.
And back then, I was craving
my dad's braised fish.
You barely escaped,
and you now want to kill a fish?
But didn't they say
eating fish makes you smarter?
I want to be smart and stay at Lime
to learn from you.
How did you know
to hit the corner
of the window to smash it open?
I saw it on the news.
I didn't know it'd work.
It seems like your brain
isn't as empty as I thought.
‪-There they are.
‪-Over there.
Luke! Shang Zhitao.
They are there. We found them.
- Over there!
- It's them!
- That's them.
- Looks like they're hurt.
‪Call 120.
‪Get them to a hospital.
HEALTH FIRST, EXPERT CARE
Nurse,
where is the guy on the bed?
Passed out
due to an intracranial hemorrhage.
He was just sent to a major hospital
for emergency treatment.
He…
But he was fine last night.
Most acute damage only appears
several hours
after the wound is inflicted.
You won't notice it at the time,
and when you do, it's too late.
Where is he? I have to find him.
Wait.
What's the hurry?
Aren't you the one
being rushed to emergency?
Can you not jinx me?
It's the other patient.
The filming is over.
I'll send you back to Beijing later.
I hope I didn't cause any delays.
Now is not the time for this.
Eat now.
Flora. Let's reflect on your work.
Do you think you handled
this project well?
I shouldn't have acted on my own.
I lacked danger awareness.
I caused trouble for everyone.
What about teamwork?
It was good.
You still haven't realized
the problem, have you?
Is Kitty your boss?
Lumi and you are my bosses.
Kitty is just a senior.
A senior.
There are many seniors in the office.
Can a senior staff member
boss you around in your project?
What's the point
of your project lead then?
Are you going to ask me
to resign again this time?
Rest up. Take care of yourself.
Make sure to go through
with the follow-up examination.
If you feel unwell, go to Lumi
or me.
Thank you for the advice, Luke.
I will follow your advice from now on.
What kind of job is this?
You are a cripple now.
Come. Let me do it.
Stop. Let me do it.
Knowing your situation,
you'll probably have to rest
at home for six months. Come.
Make the company
support you for ten years.
The doctor said
- my bone wasn't affected.
- Careful.
Besides, Luan Nian got injured
while rescuing me as well.
Now is not the time to be selfless.
They are two different things.
You got injured during work,
so the company
must take full responsibility.
As for Luan Nian…
For saving your life,
devote yourself to him.
Then, you're even.
- How sweet.
- Your job habit is coming out.
No.
He is a bad person.
He gave you a hard time.
He asked you to resign.
That's workplace bullying.
No. He's a bad person.
How can our Tao fall for him?
No. Not at all.
You misunderstood.
He is
cold-faced and sharp-tongued,
but kind on the inside.
Look. He cares
about his subordinates' safety.
And he teaches me many things.
I think I might have
misjudged him previously.
- He…
- Shang Zhitao.
Did you notice that?
I…
Notice what?
You're defending him.
You're praising him.
I'm just being objective, okay?
Objective, right.
He came to my rescue alone.
Anyone would be moved by that.
Yes, he came to your rescue alone.
You two saved each other.
I am so moved by it.
Shang Zhitao.
Listen.
Be brave when you have to.
Don't miss out on the perfect guy
you ran into with your life.
Why isn't Zhu back yet?
Didn't he mention
he'd make pork rib soup today?
Oh, my mom even bought
the Harbin red sausages
that you like.
- Changing the topic?
- We…
Okay. I get it.
Let me call Zhu now
so that he'll come back
to boil the pork rib soup
and give you the nutrients you need.
Anything you want to add?
- That's all.
- Nothing.
- Sign the contract then.
- Okay.
- That's all.
Dismissed.
I'm heading to Finance.
Colin, bring my laptop over.
Luan Nian.
I heard someone
almost died in your project.
That is scary.
I hope the client
didn't give you a hard time.
Projects always come with risks.
After all, not everyone can rely on luck
and copy someone else's idea as you do.
Ideas are meant to bounce off each other.
The difference
between inspiration and plagiarism
is similar to the difference
between a professional and you.
How is it?
Did you enjoy cleaning up the huge mess
you snatched from me?
That's one of Lime's biggest clients.
Of course, it is.
But somehow, when you manage it,
half of the client's budget is axed,
and you had to work overtime
to fix the presentation deck.
How's your sleep?
Your eye bags
are about to fall on the floor.
Don't you have work to do?
Flora.
Lumi.
Why did you come to work?
You can barely walk.
It's fine. I went to get
my follow-up examination.
The doctor said
I just needed to rest for two days.
I forgot to take my laptop,
so I came to check on everything.
This is a work injury.
Lime will not exploit you.
They even bought insurance for you.
Just stay at home and rest up.
Go back.
Actually, I want to thank Luke.
Of course.
But don't buy him any gifts.
You can buy him a meal.
I'll think about it.
Yes!
A new record.
We got it. We are just too amazing.
What a stellar result.
I need to share something with you.
I just got news
that our team
secured the Mulanshuo project
for annual advertising.
Thank you for your hard work
the past three months.
But as usual, we'll celebrate later.
We still have work to finish.
Make sure the online operations
go smoothly this week.
We'll gather here every morning
at 8:00 a.m. for a daily briefing report.
- Okay?
- Sure.
‪Give it a quick touch-up.
While everyone's here today,
let's have a recap of the project.
As you all know,
a major incident took place
during the day of filming.
Mr. Luan,
I meant to find
an opportunity to explain to you.
I wasn't shirking my duty that day.
The script was changed last minute,
so I needed
to discuss it with the director.
I was busy, so I asked Flora to help me.
I'll make sure
to keep this in mind moving forward.
So what's the point
of sending you over to assist?
I…
I didn't know Shang Zhitao was new here.
I thought she could handle it.
And everyone said
that she knew that place very well,
so I let her handle it.
Who is everyone?
My management style is quite simple.
Regardless of your experience,
those who won't take responsibility
will be replaced
by those who will.
Flora is new.
She wanted to prove herself
and was eager to take on tasks.
- I can't stop her.
- Kitty.
You have not been promoted
for three years.
I understand that you see
the new hire as a threat,
but that doesn't mean you should lie.
Shang Zhitao invited the director
over from Guangzhou herself.
What do you mean she needed you
to manage the director?
What's done is done.
Now, we need to solve the problem.
This time, everyone
on the management level,
including me, has to take accountability.
One, it was our oversight.
Two,
we did not train
our new employee adequately.
Lime will punish all relevant personnel,
including me.
Lumi's report yesterday
mentioned Flora specifically.
I plan to confirm her position.
Are you okay with it?
You have the final say.
I can never say no.
And I thought you finally
acknowledged her capabilities
and my taste.
You sure have a peculiar taste.
So, I'll proceed then.
Look at this.
LIME ADVERTISING EMPLOYMENT CONTRACT
EMPLOYEE: SHANG ZHITAO
Employment contract?
Your performance
in your first position was impressive.
I have talked to Luke.
He agreed to let you stay
at Business Division One.
Do you want the position?
Yes.
Then, sign the contract.
Thank you, Tracy.
No need to thank me.
Everyone saw how diligent
and responsible you are.
You earned the contract yourself.
Keep it up.
I… I'll continue to work hard.
Beijing is harsh but fair.
But in Lime,
if you work hard,
you will get something back.
Do you have time?
I would like
to buy you a meal to thank you.
No need.
I'll buy you a meal tonight.
Send me the address.
I'll pick you up.
Hug me tighter.
Careful.